let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What position does Harry play in Quiddtich in his first year?",
    answer: "Seeker",
    options: [
      "Seeker",
      "Sweeper",
      "Chaser",
      "Quaffle"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who is the ghost of Slytherin?",
    answer: "The Bloody Baron",
    options: [
      "Salazar Slytherin",
      "The Bloody Baron",
      "Nearby Headless Ghost",
      "Doby"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who made Harry's Wand?",
    answer: "Ollivander",
    options: [
      "Ollivander",
      "Grindelwald",
      "Gregorovitch",
      "Griphook"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who is Harry dissappointed to lean is a cousion of Sirius?",
    answer: "Bellatrix Lestrange",
    options: [
      "Cornelius Fudge",
      "Professor Snape",
      "Dolores Umbridge",
      "Bellatrix Lestrange"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What happens if you break the Unbreakable Vow?",
    answer: "You die",
    options: [
      "You die",
      "You have a hearing at the Ministery Of Magic",
      "You are cursed",
      "You are banished to the Forbodden Forest"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "In what house is Malfoy?",
    answer: "Slytherin",
    options: [
      "Ravenclaw",
      "Hufflepuff",
      "Slytherin",
      "Griffindor"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What does Rita Skeeter call Bathilda Bagshot?",
    answer: "Batty",
    options: [
      "Betty",
      "Batty",
      "Baggy",
      "Barmy"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who dies during the Triwizard Tournament?",
    answer: "Cedric Diggory",
    options: [
      "Frank Bryce",
      "Cedric Diggory",
      "Fleur Delacour",
      "Victor Krum"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Under whose order did Snape kill Dumbledore?",
    answer: "Dumbledore",
    options: [
      "Voldemort",
      "His own",
      "Belatrix Lestrange",
      "Dumbledore"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What Item does Harry steal form Gringotts? ",
    answer: "The Hufflepuff Cup",
    options: [
      "The Ring of Marvolo Gaunt",
      "The Sword of Griffindor",
      "The Hufflepuff Cup",
      "The Lost Diadem of Ravenclaw"
   ]
  },
];